DHOOM (2004)
Subtitle improved by
TharangaDE
("Dilbar Shikdum"  Performed by
Shaan and Shreya Ghoshal)
♪ Let's Shikdum. ♪
♪ When no one's around
but you and me... ♪
♪ is a moment I cherish,
so you see... ♪
♪ let's get naughty the
rest, we'll see. ♪
♪ No one's around
but you and me, ♪
♪ magic moments I cherish,
so you see... ♪
♪ let's get naughty the
rest, we'll see. ♪
♪ Come on darling. ♪
♪ no more teasing. ♪
♪ go easy. ♪
♪ don't be crazy. ♪
♪ Sweetheart lets dance. ♪
♪ Windows wish curtains...
would hide us... ♪
♪ I wish you...
wouldn't punish us. ♪
♪ let go of me.. ♪
♪ let me go. ♪
♪ Please don't push me. ♪
♪ What's your crib? ♪
♪ Why are you evasive? ♪
♪ You're very crazy. ♪
♪ I know you. ♪
♪ Sweetheart lets dance. ♪
♪ No teasing with smiles. ♪
♪ Only kisses and cuddles. ♪
♪ Okay, okay I give up. ♪
♪ I'll do, what you want. ♪
♪ Don't talk...
this moment away. ♪
♪ Then lose yourself in me. ♪
♪ Sweetheart lets dance. ♪
♪ When no one's around
but you and me... ♪
♪ is a moment I cherish,
so you see... ♪
♪ let's get naughty the
rest, we'll see. ♪
♪ Come on darling. ♪
♪ no more teasing. ♪
♪ go easy. ♪
♪ don't be crazy. ♪
♪ Sweetheart lets dance. ♪
JAI: Hello.
Speaking.
Yes go on.
What?
When?
Okay coming.
SWEETY: Stupid.
Cruel.
Work, work and work..
all the time.
and no time for me.
So why do i bother?
Don't you get back home.
Don't come back to me.
Reporting from Marine Drive.
A Safeguard security van..
was ambushed here.
Suspects are members.
of a four-biker gang...
who allegedly pulled off heists
like this one.
SHEKHAR: Where?
in there.
in there what?
TV?
Mechanic?
Police.
Yes, everyone around is a policeman.
This is a police barrier.
ACP Jai Dixit.
Expected tomorrow. Come later.
- ACP Jai Dixit.
- Sir,
Four bikes sir. Imported.
There was a police patrol
at the intersection.
Some malfunction
in traffic signaling...
Still malfunctioning.
Signal.
What...?
Find a computer expert.
Check out the signal.
May have been tampered
by someone in that gang.
Not tough. Little chip.
Anyone can reset timings.
Sir... I only heard about you.
Now I see... sorry sir...
I didn't quite make you out.
And you'll make out thieves?
Who are the guys ?
Who'd use bikes like those?
Catch one,
You've caught them all.
Where's Ali Bhai?
(Bhai: big brother)
Trailing
Uncle...
- Yes?
- 500 from my side
- On Sunny?
- Ali Bhai.
Ali Bhai?
You're a loser, kid
You cracked every record.
Fencing the bike...
- couldn't have cashed so much.
- Yes
- Now let's have a fun party
- Yes fun
ALI:
What's problem with me?
Why won't ladies give me looks?
They're just sisters
cheering their loser brothers.
Rotten bad luck.
God gives everything.
but this mess up in
ladies' department.
Even I want to become family.
Sure
Mummy, you hearing?
Ali?
Ali, that's your name?
God just heard you.
Mummy's up there.
- Ali myself.
- Hi.
I'm a great fan of yours.
Actually, you ride so well.
You're great.
Mention not.
You also sell bikes?
- You want a bike?
- Yes
You need a bike, you got mine.
Welcome to take a ride.
No actually, it's my gift to Polly.
Polly's who... sister?
Great sense of humour.
Polly, My boyfriend.
Ali Bhai, not to feel down.
Yes, not to feel down.
Oneday, you'll find someone.
Yes yes, you will.
Not one day, I want one now.
Mummy, send me someone.
In a day or two.
No, right now.
Job or wife?
Lunch on time or heartburn.
Radish-in-bread
Yogurt shake in the flask.
Not for charity.
Isn't worth the pain when I'm told.
that you never got to eat any.
Bye Baby.
Okay. Listen...
you can get home early.
for cauliflower-in-bread.
Listen...
Come on Sweety.
My sweet baby bye.
Who do you think you are?
One lifetime in jail...
then you might improve.
What?
Don't what me. If I didn't stop you.
you'd run over this poor soul.
But it isn't hurt, is it?
What'd you do after it got hurt?
If an accident never happened.
never means accidents never happen.
Okay, my mistake. Now what?
- Say sorry to it
- What...?
He won't say sorry to a man.
who escaped a brush with his car?
Correct. Sorry, you must say.
Sorry.
Hello... anyone heard anything?
- No
- I said it...
- You should say amiably, right?
- Okay
Sorry.
Loathes even your sorry.
Save the dog.
Dog bhai... stop.
Why are you staring darling?
As long as I'm around
nothing's happening to you.
Don't be afraid.
I'm a vet Sweetheart.
Come darling.
How are you feeling?
- Your name?
- Ali.
You're very brave.
You've saved a life
- His...?
- Yes.
Sorry about your accident...
Please, not to be formal.
So sweet.
Sit, I'll fix a dish for you.
- What?
- Carrot souffle.
Carrot souffle... how caring.
- Your name?
- Sweety.
What a four-stroke name.
Thank you Mummy.
for sending me a full-beautiful bride.
Perfect.
Sweety, puppy and I.
Small family, happy family.
- Who's there?
- I'll take it
Yes?
Jai, he's Ali.
Ali, that's Jai.
My husband.
Why does this happen
... to me all the time?
- What've you brought home?
- He's darling.
Darling? You call him that?
Because he's so cute.
Poor little thing
was out on the streets.
Sweety,
I've put up with all kinds
of animals for your sake.
But I never imagined...
you'd pick up a guy off the streets.
Guy...?
How silly of me. no not he, darling.
Darling's him. He's Ali, poor thing.
How true... no?
Hello.
So you live off the streets or
do you do something?
Engineer-type jobs,
I run a garage.
Ask in Bandra, every
soul knows Ali.
Ali... for you.
Anytime you want carrot souffle,
just come over, Okay!
- Promise.
- Yes sure.
- You'll want the box back?
- Whenever you come next time.
Bye Darling.
- Poor soul.
- Poor...?
I think your Ali has thief
written all over his face.
God! Will you ever change?
You're always suspecting everyone.
And it's terrible of you
and I've told you that..
Good morning Sir.
He's... He's Ali.
Operates out of a garage in Bandra.
Quick on bikes.
And a thief? Sure?
Sure sir !
I trailed him for two days.
Also fences stolen bikes.
I'm sure he belongs to the gang.
Ali's Bike Point, Bandra Lake.
Red CBR Fireblade.
Blue CBR.
Someone rapping?
Ali?
- How are you?
- Cool. And you?
Carrot souffle. From Sweety.
Hey Vinod?
Send in two teas. Special.
Nice.
Fond of bikes?
Sure.
On bikes, he'll work any original into...
- a more powerful machine.
- Really?
Makes Ali Bhai
world-famous in Mumbai.
You never told him...?
Your bikes...
Hey! Calm up.
Yaks crap.
Then you're also a biker?
Biker? He makes a bike fly.
No touchdowns, Ali's bikes fly.
He just won a race.
On that bike...
2 km lead... left the rest clutching.
You mean, here's the fastest bike?
- In Ali Bhai's hands...
- It is
Can I?
- A bike interest?
- Yes of course.
Been mulling over buying a bike,
fast racing-type.
And Sweety likes bikes too.
Want a bike?
Why not?
But I want a new bike. Fast.
Fast, like this.
New, but... no papers.
Will do?
No papers? Means?
You want to ride a bike or papers?
Takes two minutes to make paper.
But where's the bike?
Right here. You'll find anything.
Hi Rafik, all fine?
If you're new in Mumbai
you won't know.
Here's Flea Market.
Only name more famous than mine.
Out of my way.
- Stay here. Be quiet.
- Why?
Around here everyone's
a loose cannon.
Speak no evil, hear no evil.
- And you?
I got source codes, my settings.
No one's afraid of the police?
Bloody copper who walks in here
leaves his neck behind.
Afraid? Worry not.
So long as you're staring
at only dirt...
nothing happens to you.
I'll be back.
Sharp?
Or blind?
Who are you eyeballing?
Eyes down... Down.
In dirt Don't...turn me on.
One flick Lands you over there.
Do it.
What? Come again.
Slap me.
He's mad!
Doesn't know who he's taking on.
I'll save him after the first few.
Stay right here.
Want to take on Mad Anwar?
If you're not a bastard son.
you'll wait.
I'll kill you... right now Run.
What?
Run.
- You're in Shetty's gang?
- Who...?
Or Manchekar? Rodrick's? Billu?
- Which gang do you work for?
- Copper gang.
Cop... you? Shrunk him in one swipe.
...no such spunk in cops.
Ever faced off cops?
Spent my life making ass of cops.
Whatever you want to make,
never make a cop.
One quirk. How you got this
interest in bikes?
Come clean, yes?
Any idea on bank-loot?
No! Too scared of the police.
Cops? Can never catch up.
Never fear so long as
Ali rides even a bicycle.
Is it! Some faith in yourself.
I trust a cop not to catch a thief
when he knows a thief.
Stupid.
These policemen are so stupid...
so damn stupid.
- Go right in.
- They're fun.
Once I conned this one
... shined him bright.
That was one solid wallop,
I'll give you that.
Pull over.
What's this joint?
My office.
You're police?
No. Hitter.
- Scribble.
- What?
How long you've been stealing,
Dens, hideaways, accomplices, etc...
Come on.
Right from start,
I had doubts about you.
I save you and you give me
a back-kick?
We're both short of time.
Admit your guilt,
I'll try a plea bargain.
Hey Sir, Wrong rhyme.
I'm not a thief.
Look, I'm being even with you.
Just tell me what you're planning.
Who are the others in your gang?
Only Chhotu, Munna and Vinod.
Vinod is green,
can't even ride a bike.
How can I pull off a heist?
Look you can't harass me.
Not like this...
Why is he taking off his specs?
Stop him. No illegal act.
- Stop chatting the phone.
- Hey, Ali...
Look, I'm losing my mind.
Your plans, Next robbery. When?
No idea, Sir.
Sir,
- Next heist..
- Happened.
- Next robbery...
- Just happened.
What?
A robbery. A while ago. In Andheri.
They are taking the highway.
KABIR:
Welcome to Pizza Place.
What will you have?
Good evening sir.
Any leads Jai? Any clues?
Camera locations, police positions,
our reaction times,
they knew everything.
They left us no clues.
They're professionals.
Jai, What's happening?
I mean, this is too much.
Getting away with daylight robbery,
...it's a slur on us.
- Sir, I think we're going wrong.
- How?
All along we were thinking
like policemen.
Now... We got to think like thieves.
If they're sharp,
we got to get sharper.
They use bikes for getaways.
- We use bikes to get them.
- But our riders are on it.
Not our men.
- Someone else.
- Who?
- Jai hit you?
- Who else?
And I tell you this,
please don't mind.
For what law-abiding
policeman he is...
He's really a hood.
- Such a terrible grinding.
- Don't be afraid.
I'll give him a hollering.
Let him come
I'm not staying on.
He'll put me through the grind again.
If he lets go, I lose face value.
I'm quitting.
My home is no jailhouse.
He'll face me if he touches you.
Meanwhile, Carrot souffle.
Excuse me.
I knew I'd find you here.
Just returning the box. Bye.
Come. Where're you going?
Carrot souffle before you leave?
What's coming over you?
Not another con?
Who is it?
Shall I tell Sweety that you
fence stolen bikes?
She despises thieves.
If she knows, no more carrot,
only stick.
- No entry for you in here.
- Who's there?
Jai...
Big brother.
Jai, what's this I hear?
You hit Ali?
I... Can I hit anybody?
- I hit you?
- No.
I fell off the bike.
Sweety, Why would I
hit this poor guy?
He didn't get what
I was getting at.
I took him to the police station
because he's working for me.
Yes, I was telling him
how he can help us.
For that I took him to
the police station.
But poor guy got me all wrong.
How wonderful Ali,
You're scared for nothing.
Great Jai.
See Ali? Jai isn't all that ugly.
He'll take good care of you.
Darling, let's go inside.
Good care of me...
Sums all my fears
Working for you? Doing what?
I'm doing nothing.
You guys work life's dangers.
I'm not into it.
Hmm. OK. This is for you.
Sweety gets to see it.
then others.
- Getting at what, big brother?
- For a minimum of 3 years...
Your boys get to
manage your garage.
Why are you after me?
Don't peel the specs.
You're fine how you are.
Tomorrow you're on
the job, Correct?
6 am Sharp.
Six am...?
Morning prayers?
Yeah. I'll give you a rosary.
And I'll take off my specs, Go..
- Photo...?
- Glasses?
- Say bye to Sweety.
- Out.
Wow!
There he is!
Wow. So that's your surprise?
Grand car, no?
- Get in and you're getting looks.
- Not him, the car.
Price? Never mind. Only takes...
a couple of jobs.
Yes Kabir? Nice?
3000 cc Zero to hundred
In ten seconds.
You should buy a car... like this.
Careful.
Good brakes too
Stops in 5 seconds.
This is scary.
- Jump.
- What?
Jump.
What have you done?
Are you mad?
Brand new car.
You're very lucky Rahul.
- You could've been in that car.
- What?
It's no waiter's car.
We bandits got to vanish like smoke.
The day cops get wind, it's all over.
No one bends my rules.
Not even I.
Colour.
Oh Daddy! I got a trio.
Thank you Mummy.
I got some luck, no?
One more, one more.
We're raising stakes now.
Per head... 500.
Quick.
If hotshot Robin Hood finds out,
he'll grill me. He puts me off.
Hey, Tenner? for what?
- Big brother.
- For Band Aid.
Next heist is here. This area.
How can you be so sure Jai?
There's a pattern.
November 20, Borivali.
November 26, Kandivali.
November 30, Malad.
December 5, Andheri.
December 8, Vile Parle.
In each of the five heists,
the robbers and their bikes
vanished without a trace.
All in a trice. But how?
Five incidents...
One common factor...
Western Express Highway.
Always...
within a 2 or 3 minute drive
from the highway.
So I think, the next target... is here.
Any intelligence?
On identities or
allegiances to gangs?
This gang works for themselves.
No past record or history.
In this city... they can be
anyone, anywhere.
They can only be caught in the act.
Because, after the hits...
how they masquerade,
we shall never know.
How to know when next?
Soon enough, sir.
Five hits in 20 days.
They're rewing up for a finale.
Before they go extinct.
I think that's their plan.
But this time,
we'll be staking it out.
Shekhar come in.
Shekhar here sir.
Shekhar, Cover my position. Copy?
Copy that sir.
You're here, I know it
Show yourself once.
Flower Make me a nice.
Bouquet for 10 bucks.
A whole bouquet for a tenner?
Okay, for whom?
Now you're asking. For my wife to-be.
I got to be a family.
No joking on duty. If the boss gets
to see, we'll have a problem.
Who's scared of your boss?
Mind your business. Sell me a bouquet.
- Make do with this rose.
- One rose for 10?
Just...
Shekhar, you take a break.
- Get back at 6 am tomorrow.
- Okay sir
Me too.
Hey?
Home. Sweety has cooked chicken.
Until we've caught them, you
aren't going anywhere, got it?
We stay rooted, even if they
don't turn up for a week?
Why? You are too busy?
Want to inaugurate a jail?
But Sweety's chicken...
Never heard of contact lenses?
I'll eat on time.
Okay. Bye.
Sweety, I'm working.
Okay.
Yes, I love you too. Bye.
What?
Go on.
- First, Promise.
- What?
- Not to hit me.
- No.
What no? You won't hit me
or you won't promise me?
Can't promise I won't hit you.
Then I'm not telling.
Okay, you can tell me.
You ought to know, Sweety
would've married me,
What?
That's if I had met her before...
But it's okay.
She was more ravishing
then or now?
You want a bashing now or later?
Must've been arranged marriage.
It was arranged for you, yes?
Admit it.
Hello, Sweety.
There's an envelope on the table.
My photos inside it?
No please, Sweety mustn't see.
It's there?
Big brother... My reputation.
- She won't see my face.
- Who?
Sweety... Your wife.
What else?
Keep it in my study, Thanks, Bye.
Yes. I love you too.
Don't cry for me, Mummy.
- His heart has turned to stone
- Will you shut up?
- Sit tight.
- What?
I mean... Public... Public distress.
And sleeping police?
This is catastrophe.
Public help! It's a police slogan.
You're making her helpless.
Some guy, by God.
Okay, You sit tight.
Let me help.
I'm a mechanic.
It's my religion.
Starting up stalled cars
... is religion
SHEENA: Excuse me.
My car seem to have broken down,
Could you, Help me out please...
("Dilbara" Performed
by Abhijeet and Sowmya Rao)
♪ Rum Raagta Rigiri Raagta ♪
♪ Rum Raagta Rigiri Raagta Rum ♪
♪ Sweetheart, Sweetheart, ♪
♪ You're mine, I'm yours. ♪
♪ Let me love you, ♪
♪ Make a family with you. ♪
♪ That is all my wish for today. ♪
Started it all over again.
♪ Sweetheart, Sweetheart, ♪
♪ You're mine, I'm yours. ♪
♪ Let me love you, ♪
♪ Make a family with you. ♪
♪ That is all my wish for today. ♪
Forget it. Not happening for you.
♪ Yes. You only You. ♪
♪ I'm yours. ♪
Incorrigible
♪ No family, ♪
♪ I'm lonely. ♪
♪ My home's lovely, ♪
♪ Heart's lonely. ♪
♪ Rum Raagta Rigiri Raagta ♪
♪ Rum Raagta Rigiri Raagta Rum ♪
♪ I'm lonely, ♪
♪ No family. ♪
♪ My home's lovely, ♪
♪ My heart's lonely. ♪
♪ My dreams... ♪
♪ So far they seem... ♪
♪ in a life, without a wife. ♪
♪ You're lonely, ♪
♪ even I'm lonely. ♪
♪ You're lively, So hopefully... ♪
♪ You and I... make a family. ♪
♪ Sweetheart, Sweetheart, ♪
♪ You're mine, I'm yours. ♪
♪
♪ I think you're crazy. ♪
♪ Make very nice excuses. ♪
♪ Rum Raagta Rigiri Raagta ♪
♪ Rum Raagta Rigiri Raagta Rum ♪
♪ I think you're crazy. ♪
♪ Making very nice excuses. ♪
♪ Still how can I fall for you? ♪
♪ I still don't know you. ♪
♪ Wait for another day. ♪
♪ I'll decide what to say. ♪
Fast girl.
♪ Sweetheart, Sweetheart, ♪
♪ You're mine, I'm yours. ♪
♪ Let me love you, ♪
♪ Make a family with you. ♪
♪ That is all my wish for today. ♪
♪ Sweetheart, Sweetheart, ♪
♪ You're mine, I'm yours. ♪
Gone. Back to work.
- Shekhar?
- Yes Sir, Hello, Sir.
- Over here.
- No pranks.
- You'll do one favour for me.
- Which?
- I got to find this sweetheart.
- You need addresses, photos.
Given all that, even I can find her.
You police guys are so hopeless, really.
- Shekhar?
- I warn you.
Take the left gate.
Post me every 5 minutes.
OK, Sir.
Yeah, Repeat. OK.
Copy that.
Sir, One question, Sir.
I got to improve my
general knowledge.
..and you're what a
walking law school.
Shut up.
No, shut up.
Keep shut, do the job.
Bikes. Coming.
Not coming...
Moving away from us.
Go. Get them.
Don't let them escape.
At 260...
I'm doing full throttle.
He's over 300.
Damn!
- Hi.
Serve table 12.
Must do something about him.
Not here.
Rohit is my brother.
He could've died.
I said, not here.
- Fetch the order for table 12
- Damn table 12
I'm not sparing that cop.
I'll do what's to be done.
You don't tax your brains.
- Kabir?
- Good evening, Sir.
- Good evening. Table for 2 please.
Rohit, Upstairs.
TV REPORTER: Fighting
the spurt in crime...
...is ACP Jai Dixit.
Jai? You're on TV.
TV REPORTER: You solved
your cases in record time.
Except this bike gang.
What's taking you so long?
You've seen rats stealing?
He grabs a steal...
and runs for his hole.
That's how this bike gang is...
Like rats..
They wear masks.
Then they vanish.
We foiled one of their operations.
Hopefully... this gang,
won't bother us for long.
A message for the audience?
You'll see the defeat
on their faces soon.
For the gang, what's
your message?
Maybe they're
watching TV right now
No madam. I don't
talk to criminals.
Thank you sir.
That was ACP Jai Dixit.
For rest of the news,
watch 'Aaj Tak'
- I feel... like...
- Be cool.
Don't bill him.
Men like him don't drop in every day.
- Take care of him.
- Yes boss.
Must take good care of him.
I'll take good care of him.
Well done, Jai.
So what if we didn't
catch the thieves,
their loot... we retrieved.
That bike sir, will tell us
why they're so fast.
- Ali?
- Hold.
Dr. Ali's operation successful.
Wonderful engineering.
Main thing, Nitrous Oxide cylinder.
Know what it does?
Flick of a switch...
bike becomes a rocket...
Another highlight
Trigger for timer.
- What's more...
- Good, very good.
- Jai, what's our next step?
- They've taken a beating.
It's their turn to make a move.
For you.
Hello?
- Didn't call for hello-hi
- Who?
If I'm telling it all,
what're you doing?
How will you give
grand TV interviews?
Then you heard me.
I don't talk to criminals.
- See you in jail.
- Thanks for the offer.
But I'm not destined for jail.
Got yourself one grand destiny,
Great brains too. but...
future looks somewhat shady.
Really?
Yes. You took the pains to call me.
It's my duty to keep you warned.
I like your style.
Perhaps you're too confident, no?
Tell me your address.
I'll deliver the bike and the money.
Will help your confidence too..
Say what you will.
you'll never catch me.
Hey, Don't play hero.
You're a thief.
You'll run, I'll catch you.
I'll walk right through you.
You won't even recognise me.
For once, show up. You won't be
worth recognising anymore.
OK. I'll come right up to you.
I'll even tell you about my next hit.
Where will you find thieves like me?
You find thieves only in jails.
I'll see you right there.
My next time, my next target,
You'll know beforehand.
If you nab me, it's my neck.
- If I escape...
- Impossible...
I love the impossible Mr. Dixit.
But one little clause.
If you fail...
you'll drop the case.
- What happened? Afraid?
- Where?
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
Where are you headed?
Up ahead.
I'll take you. Come.
I'll manage. Don't waste your time.
Helping is no waste of time. Careful.
Very few like you around nowadays.
Untrue.
Not exactly the age
of good Samaritans.
Sir, No matter how rapid
the evil strides.
the good is always
a march ahead.
- Saying something?
- But how, Kabir?
The police will be there in force.
Politicians are coming.
It's a high security zone.
Getting inside will be tough,
as for pulling it off...
We steal.
Right in front of everyone.
And we'll make a getaway in public.
Trust me.
Bullets... can outspeed our bikes.
Not in bullets.
Speed is a shooter's spunk.
("Dhoom Machale"
Performed by Sunidhi Chauhan)
♪ Let's Rock! ♪
♪ You want to love, do love. ♪
♪ In love, you can live, ♪
♪ you can die. ♪
♪ Love is most cherished of all. ♪
♪ You want to love, do love. ♪
♪ Love, ♪
♪ To do or die for. ♪
♪ Never comes again. ♪
♪ Love... is life. ♪
♪ Love is... joy. ♪
♪ Give in to love... ♪
♪ ...and swing. ♪
♪ Let's Rock! ♪
♪
♪ What is love afterall? ♪
♪ Ask someone, ♪
♪ Who's crazy. ♪
♪ it happen like this, ♪
♪ it burn like this, ♪
♪ Ask Yourself Why? ♪
♪ What is love afterall? ♪
♪ Ask someone, ♪
♪ Who's crazy. ♪
♪ it happen like this, ♪
♪ it burn like this, ♪
♪ Ask Yourself Why? ♪
♪ Love is short, dear. ♪
♪ Love happens once, dear. ♪
♪ Kiss the shadow of love. ♪
♪ Let's Rock! ♪
♪
♪ Nobody can live in loneliness. ♪
♪ Every soul here knows. ♪
♪ Dear stranger, you don't know. ♪
♪ What my heart has done. ♪
♪ You must do this crime also. ♪
♪ Nobody can live in loneliness. ♪
♪ Every soul here knows. ♪
♪ Dear stranger, you don't know. ♪
♪ What my heart has done. ♪
♪ You must do this crime also. ♪
♪ Make every loving moment rock. ♪
♪ Love's makes your heart rock. ♪
♪ Come, sway in the path of love. ♪
♪ Let's Rock! ♪
Over? No, Can't do.
I've only arrived.
Guys... What's the vote?
- Once more.
♪
♪ You want to love, do love. ♪
♪ In love, you can live, ♪
♪ you can die. ♪
♪ Love is most cherished of all. ♪
♪ You want to love, do love. ♪
♪ In love, you can live, ♪
♪ you can die. ♪
♪ Love is most cherished of all. ♪
♪ Life is love. ♪
♪ Every happiness is love. ♪
♪ Lose yourself in love. ♪
♪ Let's Rock! ♪
Ladies and Gentlemen,
The proceeds from this show goes to the
Chief Minister's Relief Fund.
The amount is... Rs. 42,50,000.
Have a look.
- The money...?
- Where is it?
Sweetheart... Ambulance.
What happened sir?
I saw them in Pizza Place.
They were waiters.
Are we going there?
No use. We won't find anyone there.
Ali?
How much did you sell out for?
This sweetheart... She swooned.
- How much money?
- Not my fault.
I tell you...
No discounts on courtesy.
Brother, if I let go.
You'll get a changed face.
On the bike, It's your job.
Not the girl.
TV REPORTER: Once again...
The mysterious bike gang,
...has struck.
Sending the city into a tizzy.
Sources indicate that... the police were
tipped off... well in advance.
As usual they could achieve nothing.
Jai Dixit, despite all your efforts...
the bike gang got away with it?
Not because they're exceptional.
The mistake was mine.
I made a very big mistake.
Therefore on moral grounds.
I am dropping this case,
And I'm resigning.
- And that mechanic?
- He's no longer on the team.
Clarify the..
I think you know what I mean.
Excuse me.
That's Jai Dixit.
Rahul.
Where are you going?
Not a cop any longer,
so no sparing him.
Foolish. Killing him
won't bring back Rohit.
We've lots more to do.
Get on the job.
Who does Rohit's job?
Without him, the next job
isn't getting done.
Get ready to quit this city.
I'll take care of loose ends.
- What's wrong with Ali Bhai?
- Very early lead.
Too late... the race is on.
What are you racing for?
Who's that?
He's fast!
Sorry guys.
Never mind, It happens.
We've made loads out of you.
- One race makes no difference.
- Still, you lost money.
Luckless day.
Scrapped with Jai. Then Sweetheart
vanishes from the hospital.
Made me want to burn the track.
Here, I'm run out.
I really want to wreck
that guy in black.
What man?
- I don't take charity.
- I'm not racing for money.
What I'm looking for
money won't buy.
Am I game? No way.
I don't fancy getting
shot by the police.
The police can't even touch you.
...and you know it.
Or are you scared?
If I could, I would drown
every cop in the sea...
beginning with Jai.
After pumping him so hard,
Harder than I care to tell you.
Then why hesitate?
How to find confidence in you?
You can be a cop.
Not a copper has set sight
on this face.
Never will you might
not think so.
but I know you're worth millions.
Don't waste your life, Ali.
If I tell the cops, that
I've seen you.
I'm up for the reward.
I think you already got a reward
for working with the police.
I'm sure you aren't going
anywhere near them.
6 am tomorrow, Khopoli.
At the crossroads.
I'll see you there.
Hey,
I'm not an early riser.
Your luck is changing.
You'll change.
Mummy was always telling me Ali,
You're smart and you're fast.
- You want to be smart and fast?
- Sure.
Just open up.
Now close it.
Tony Bhai.
Ali, something's odd about my bike.
- What?
- The firing.
I'll change my name,
if I can't fix it.
- What will you name yourself? Rohit?
- Mummy gave me a great name.
So why change it. Sorry Tony,
No changing names. Rahul is right.
Rahul Bhai, you can tell me
whenever your bike sneezes.
Don't touch it.
You'll take Rohit's place?
He's dead. Because of you.
I'm on your side now, brother.
I'm not your brother.
I fly off my handle,
You end up a sissy.
You bloody.
Boys!
Take it easy.
I don't like his face.
And I don't like your face.
Nor you like mine.
We're not friends.
But we need each other.
That's it.
After we're done this time,
no one will have any need left.
Neither to steal nor
to tolerate each other.
So stop the infighting.
I want all six of us
over here at sunset.
Let's get down to
some serious work.
Kabir brother, Listen...
You're a great guy.
But one little mistake.
We're five of us, not six.
Mannu, Tony, myself,
- Mr Boom-bastic and you. Five.
- Not five. Six.
Start counting,
Mannu, Tony, myself...
Ali...
♪ Let's Rock! ♪
♪ Dhoom Dhoom ♪
♪ Come and light my fire. ♪
♪ Let me take u higher. ♪
♪ Dhoom Dhoom ♪
♪ Wanna feel that burning. ♪
♪ It' s a wild emotion. ♪
♪ Dhoom Dhoom ♪
♪ Passion and devotion. ♪
♪ Now the wheels are turning. ♪
♪ Move ur body close to mine now. ♪
♪ Let me feel ur love divine now. ♪
♪ Together we will explode, ♪
♪ and we will go.. ♪
♪ Boom Boom Boom Boom ♪
♪ Dhoom Machale, ♪
♪ Dhoom Machale Dhoom. ♪
♪ Let's Rock! ♪
♪ Dhoom Machale, ♪
♪ Dhoom Machale Dhoom. ♪
♪ Let's Rock! ♪
♪ Dhoom Machale, ♪
♪ Dhoom Machale Dhoom. ♪
Thank you. Thank you, Mummy.
Hey, Topclass acting.
Dance, romance, works.
I sent you on an ambulance ride.
And I find you riding waves.
Wonderful sweetheart.
Sheena.
My name is Sheena.
And whatever I did with you
was part of my job.
My job. So you and me...
Never think of it.
What Mummy...
You send me one girl,
and she's a hood.
Too many hassles in life.
Taj Exotica. Largest,
Grandest hotel in Goa.
Yes! Lovely hotel, Kabir.
But we're thieves, not tourists.
What the hell are we doing here?
Look at it through a thief's eyes...
and you'll see 180 million bucks.
India's biggest casino.
Fortunes are made everyday,
and... lost.
Whatever a gambler's luck...
The casino is always...
on a winning spree.
Last year, December 31...
Raked in... 16 crores.
Takings Trucked away.
To a special vault. Once every
hour under tight security.
They are so confident
about the security system.
No video cameras are installed.
This year on December 31,
the management expects...
the casino will rake in
180 million, minimum.
180 million.
Six thieves.
Split evenly.
How much for the two of us
put together, sweetheart?
I'm bad at arithmetic.
KABIR: Ali?
It's our final hit.
Afterwards, we're free.
We will never see
one another again.
nor will we try to
contact each other.
Nice idea.
But it's a hotel, not a bank.
Teeming with people. So more risk.
Mannu says that the security system
was designed by an Israeli company.
- Opening the safe won't be easy.
- Infrared alarm at main door.
Goa police will be after
us in 30 seconds.
Kabir must've worked all that out.
What I want to know is,
How we go about it.
I'll second that question.
Whatever we do...
We do in style.
Four-stroke joint.
- We got reservations.
- Name?
Prince Ali Akbar Fateh Khan
of Secunderabad.
Of course. Of course.
Suite 101? Right?
Come, this way.
Hi Austin... Austin Powers.
You lodged a complaint?
- There's a virus in the system.
- Don't worry. I'm here to fix it.
This way, please.
We offer a choice of suites.
- Any reason for your choice?
- We're on our honeymoon.
Royal astrologer says, book into room
101 for Baby-Prince-coming-fast.
Excuse me, Sir.
Hey Tony,
- I want my money back.
- What?
- It's my money.
- It's Kabir's money.
Then give me a loan.
- Why on earth did Kabir take him on?
- Because he knows you love me secretly.
Ali? Keep that gibberish here.
Downstairs, remember
you're a Prince.
Yes. Yes. Thank you. Thank you.
Very okay, Very okay.
Exhausted your English vocabulary?
Should've saved some for tonight.
Hello Room Service.
- 101. Room service order.
- Got it.
Good you're here.
Taking charge of the bar?
What's your name?
Kabir.
You play like a seasoned gambler.
If you're so good who needs thieving?
Ali, you're a prince. Don't forget.
Sweetheart, No yakking.
Daddy is eavesdropping.
- Good evening. Everything okay?
- Yes yes. Thank you. Very okay.
One problem.
We're leaving tonight.
At quarter past twelve.
- Have we caused anything?
- No, No, No. Not yet.
Royal astrologer called
and Daddy insists. So...
- Got to go.
- We're back next week.
Wonderful! Wonderful!
Our luggage is packed.
- Please have it put in the car.
- Don't worry my dear.
Your luggage will be in your car
at quarter past twelve.
- Thank you so much.
- Enjoy. Enjoy.
Enjoy. Enjoy.
By then we've robbed the place.
Ali? I told you.
Never use the word.
Who have we to fear?
No cops around.
One whisky please.
One.. Whisky please.
What are you drinking?
Forgot.
Anything will do.
Make it quick.
Else, my wife will find out.
Here.
- Will you have a drink?
- No thanks.
I don't drink.
What? Really?
You... a bartender
who doesn't drink? How?
With... all the booze around.
Very bad.
All around, money's flying too.
But I never steal.
Very good.
You know...
I used to be a cop.
Was.
Shhh.
Never tell anyone.
They'll run scared.
I won't tell anyone that you've had
a drink and you're a police officer.
- Was.
- Okay. Was.
Thanks buddy.
Happy New Year.
Now...?
At midnight, no?
In case we don't meet.
Happy New Year in advance.
No my friend,
Of course we'll meet.
In Happy New Year
of course we'll meet.
I like you.
My drink.
Was... What I was.
ACP Jai Dixit is in the hotel.
How could this happen?
Now what to do?
- I warned you.
- Rahul.
It's serious Kabir.
Where is Ali?
- Let's get our luggage.
- What?
Let's slip out quietly.
- Kabir Bhai, you start out first.
- Relax Ali.
It's time we ran. No one knows
that psycho more than I know.
He'll crunch every bone.
Alone, he's no threat to us.
Don't underestimate him.
He's the last samurai.
I don't give a damn.
Anyway, it's New Years Eve, the whole
world is here, maybe he's just a guest.
- So, we change plans?
- No Sheena.
I waited a whole year for tonight.
My plans. Mine.
No change.
180 million. And steal
it all by myself.
Anyone who isn't with me,
isn't coming with me.
("Salaame" Performed by Kunal
Ganjawala and Vasundhara Das)
♪ Me Gusto Mucho Bailar Bailar, ♪
♪ Quiero Samba Quiero Salsa. ♪
♪ Quiero Samba Quiero Rumba. ♪
♪ Fiesta, Latina, ♪
♪ It's Driving Wild, ♪
♪ Come Salsa With Me, ♪
♪ It's Party Time… ♪
♪ Fiesta, Latina, ♪
♪ It's Driving Wild, ♪
♪ Come Salsa With Me, ♪
♪ It's Party Time… ♪
♪ Take in this wonderful night. ♪
♪ It's all in this moment, ♪
♪ It'll never come one more time. ♪
♪ Take in this wonderful night. ♪
♪ It's all in this moment, ♪
♪ It'll never come one more time. ♪
♪ To another night... ♪
♪ To another time... ♪
♪ To a new... ♪
♪ Tomorrow, Tomorrow. ♪
♪ Cheers! ♪
♪ Take in this wonderful night. ♪
♪ It's all in this moment, ♪
♪ It'll never come one more time. ♪
♪ To another night... ♪
♪ To another time... ♪
♪ To a new... ♪
♪ Tomorrow, Tomorrow. ♪
♪ Cheers! ♪
♪ Me Gusto Mucho Bailar Bailar, ♪
♪ Quiero Samba Quiero Salsa. ♪
♪ Quiero Samba Quiero Rumba. ♪
♪ La La Laai, ♪
♪ La La Laai... ♪
♪ It's wild tonight... ♪
♪ in drunken delight. ♪
♪ Earth spins at our feet. ♪
♪ We're so full of life. ♪
♪ You've only so long as you're ♪
♪ still young only so much fun. ♪
♪ Just a little flip. ♪
♪ Get a taste of the real thing. ♪
♪ To another night, ♪
♪ To another time... ♪
♪ To a new... Tomorrow. ♪
♪ Who cares what the world thinks. ♪
♪ Cheers! ♪
♪
♪ Fiesta, Latina, ♪
♪ It's Driving Wild, ♪
♪ Come Salsa With Me, ♪
♪ It's Party Time… ♪
♪ We're carefree. ♪
♪ Who cares where.. ♪
♪ This trip ends. ♪
♪ We're wild and free, ♪
♪ We're free, ♪
♪ We're different. ♪
♪ We can do what we want. ♪
♪ Whatever you hear, ♪
♪ Whatever they say, ♪
♪ Nothing's stopping us today. ♪
♪ To another night, ♪
♪ To another time. ♪
♪ To a new... ♪
♪ Tomorrow, Tomorrow. ♪
♪ Cheers! ♪
Prince, Mr. Prince..
It's Been a pleasure
to having you here.
- Same here.
- Same to same.
Everything to satisfaction?
Privacy and...?
Yes.
Your luggage.
Congratulations boys.
We've done it.
Like I said.
We meet in the new year.
Happy New Year!
- Now...?
- Your wish.
You can try running, then chasing,
then blood and gore.
Or we can depart peacefully.
Get in my car, then jail sweet jail.
It's upto you.
Let's walk.
- You do a good bit of acting.
- And you're good at stealing.
But the good is, one
march ahead of evil.
You're good.
Were you a thief,
we'd be friends.
Kabir, you break my heart.
I thought we're friends enough.
for you to write me
letters from jail.
Between friends...
You got me.
but what about the loot?
You don't have the money.
I do.
Right now Ali is
delivering the cash, Nice?
You're wasting your
time with the police.
You're very good.
Ali was with you.
You planted him.
Don't blame me.
You took him on.
That fight was a sham?
He took real blows.
Sorry if that hurts you.
After Rohit, I'd go to Ali looking
for another rider. You knew it?
No. I hoped.
Mind blowing.
Ali and you.
You got me man.
- It was a perfect plan.
- Not was.
It is a perfect plan.
One thing Jai.
Nothing is permanent
Not you, not I.
Neither plan, Nor time.
See?
Time changes.
What happened to the lights?
Check the lights.
Run Kabir.
Run for your life.
True, Sweetheart.
There's lots of money in crime.
But respectability? Not a shred.
You Fool..
- Kabir won't spare you.
- Kabir has become mincemeat.
You know Jai?
One danger-full guy.
- For a 3000 buck job...?
- Please Sweetheart.
Not just for the money.
The starched uniform is a perk.
After being with Jai, I admit.
It's a respectable job.
Once we're mister and misses...
you will...
...say it with pride.
My husband, Police.
Just say you love me
before you run for it.
I'm not running.
Even if I run,
I won't come back to you.
Guarantee! Our marriage certificate
was stamped up above. You will come.
Mummy has even thought up names
for our kids. Want to hear?
Sweetheart, here comes
their Uncle Jai.
Kabir Brother, Happy New Year!
You took long.
I was just telling Sheena.
You're late. She went off to sleep.
Bored.
What...?
Everyone warned me.
I never listened.
First ever time I failed
to make out a man.
First time.
Sheena, I guess you
hate him the most.
Hey Sweetheart.
You'll kill me?
Not here. Let's move out.
Come on, Sheena.
Come on let's go.
Rahul, She isn't coming.
Sweetheart...
They're gone. You didn't.
Now I'm relaxed.
Ali?
- Move Ali.
- Now...?
- No. I'm staying here.
- Ali. Come on.
Crazy.
I'll be back, sweetheart.
Don't vanish again.
Come on, Ali.
Yes yes. Thank you.
Very okay. Very okay.
Your timing's all out.
First time in life...
I start on a love scene.
And you get shooting.
- I could've been shot.
- Were you?
Where were you when he was
grinding me at gunpoint?
- Didn't I save you?
- My good luck. Mummy's blessings.
Thank you Mummy.
- You didn't take the bullet.
- If I did...
I'd end up in a police station.
Martyr in a photo frame.
- Police station?
- Yes... I'm a cop no?
Until we've caught them,
you're only Ali. Get it?
- So I get to die for free?
- Are you dead and gone?
But I'm going. I resign.
No life guarantee, so I resign.
You swim?
I'll resign when I touch base.
- Take me ashore.
- There.
What are you trying? Why?
Hold on.
Buckle up.
Boating on streets.
Needs a driving lesson.
Fast. Fast.
Kabir, Faster.
Jai overdrive. Overtake him.
Drive.
Come on.
Bye Boom-bastic.
Hi. Big Brother.
All fine?
You're blocking my view.
Why aren't you stopping? Stop.
Mistake. Sorry.
Sorry Jai.
Idiot.
Driving this mac was fun. So...
- You can't see?
- No...
I was dangling...
Like I said... you're thief.
You run. I get you.
Like I said...
I'll walk right through you.
You'll never catch me.
What a waste of life.
If you weren't a thief,
we would've been friends.
Now I'm a policeman?
- We'll see.
- What's that mean, man?
I ought to get a chance
to become a decent guy.
Like I said, we'll see.
Sub Inspector or Inspector?
Who's higher up?
You'll find out.
- Okay don't send Sheena to jail.
- Why? She isn't a thief?
But she's marrying a policeman.
She deserves a discount?
- A reservation in ladies' jail.
- Only if I'm posted there.
Ali?
- Yes...?
- Shut up.
♪ Dhoom Dhoom, ♪
♪ Come light my fire. ♪
♪ Let me take you hire. ♪
♪ Dhoom Dhoom, ♪
♪ I wanna feel that burning. ♪
♪ It's a wild emotion. ♪
♪ Dhoom Dhoom, ♪
♪ Passion and devotion. ♪
♪ Now the wheels are turning. ♪
♪ Move your body ♪
♪ close to mine now, ♪
♪ Let me feel your ♪
♪ love into mine now, ♪
♪ Together we'll explode ♪
♪ and we'll go... ♪
♪ Boom Boom Boom ♪
♪ Dhoom machale, ♪
♪ Dhoom machale, Dhoom. ♪
♪ Dhoom Dhoom, ♪
♪ I m gonna make you sweat now. ♪
♪ Lets get all wet now. ♪
♪ Dhoom Dhoom, ♪
♪ Gotta get down all day. ♪
♪ Till the early morning. ♪
♪ Dhoom Dhoom, ♪
♪ Until the dawn end. ♪
♪ I know that you want it. ♪
♪ Shake your body ♪
♪ down to the ground. ♪
♪ Want you all, there's ♪
♪ no turn around. ♪
♪ Tonight we're gonna ♪
♪ make the world go... ♪
♪ Boom Boom Boom ♪
♪ Dhoom machale, ♪
♪ Dhoom machale, Dhoom. ♪
♪ Dance with me.. ♪
♪ This is my philosophy. ♪
♪ Oh Yeah. ♪
♪ Dance with me.. ♪
♪ This is my philosophy. ♪
♪ Oh Yeah. ♪
♪ This burning inside you ♪
♪ know you just cannot hide, ♪
♪ So go find the feeling, ♪
♪ let your body decide. ♪
♪ When you get down on the road, ♪
♪ It's the wild overload, ♪
♪ Riding higher than ♪
♪ you ever did before. ♪
♪ Dhoom Dhoom, ♪
♪ Let your body do the talking. ♪
♪ Wanna keep on rocking. ♪
♪ Dhoom Dhoom, ♪
♪ I want it 24/7. ♪
♪ Get the rhythm of the beat now. ♪
♪ Dhoom Dhoom, ♪
♪ Feel the fire and the heat now. ♪
♪ Take a trip to heaven. ♪
♪ I wanna feel the ♪
♪ winds in my hair now, ♪
♪ Spread the power ♪
♪ everywhere now, ♪
♪ Feel the magic just go ♪
♪ zip zap...♪
♪ zoooooooooooom. ♪
♪ Dhoom machale, ♪
♪ Come on, you People, ♪
♪ Dhoom. ♪
♪ Dhoom machale, ♪
♪ Dhoom machale, Dhoom. ♪